Man's first step on the moon nearly stumbled on earth.
The Dish is a comedy, drama, history film directed by Rob Sitch.
A group of maverick scientists on a remote Australian sheep farm are the globe's only
hope for obtaining the epic images of man's first steps on the moon.
Cliff Buxton - Dish Master, played by Sam Neill.
Al Burnett - From NASA, played by Patrick Warburton.
Ross 'Mitch' Mitchell - Maneuvers, played by Kevin Harrington.
Glenn Latham - Electronics, played by Tom Long.
Janine Kellerman - The Girl, played by Eliza Szonert.
Mayor Robert 'Bob' McIntyre, played by Roy Billing.
The Dish is a 2000 Australian historical comedy-drama film that tells the story of the Parkes Observatory's role in
relaying live television of humanity's first steps on the Moon during the Apollo 11 mission in 1969.
It was the top-grossing Australian film in 2000.
The film explores themes of australia, nasa, based on
true story, moon landing, moon walk.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.